well
Thank You mr. Alec you are now protected
with Sun protector plan our kid Jack got
himself a 15 year life protection plan
that came with bonus payouts
finally he was taking a step towards his
dreams to travel around the world with
his loved one after three years he
received his first loyalty bonus the
next three years he received another
loyalty bonus and again and again on the
fifth and tenth year he continues to
receive cash rewards on his birthday was
more he received double birthday rewards
on the fifteenth year wait we're not
done yet the same year upon the maturity
of his protection plan he received 25
percent cash back on his total premiums
paid and now elegant family are on a
plane to live out their dream wish to
get your son protector plan stay tuned
we'll call you soon
[Music]